<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Tickets Booking</string>
    <string name="app_version">Version 1.3.0</string>
    <string name="project_introduction">
        Within a smartphone connecting to the Internet, we can pick a favorite movie,
        select a suitable airing time and seats for a movie ticket booking at home.
        This is a real time system connected to a clouding database, you can
        know the status of the actual theater slots and make your own choice.
    </string>

    <string name="mov_86_description">
        "86 -Eighty Six-" is a 2021-2022 anime series that centers on the conflict
        between the Republic of San Magnolia and the Empire of Giad. While the Republic
        claims to be fighting a "war without casualties" using unmanned drones,
        the reality is that young people, branded the "86," are forced to pilot those drones
        in a devastating and unequal conflict.
    </string>

    <string name="mov_josee_description">
        "Josee, the Tiger and the Fish" is a 2020 Japanese animated romance film that tells
        the story of Tsuneo, a marine biology student, and Josee, a young woman with paraplegia,
        who becomes his caretaker. The film explores themes of love, friendship, overcoming fears,
        and the beauty of embracing life challenges.
    </string>

    <string name="mov_violet_description">
        Violet Evergarden is a Japanese anime series about a young ex-soldier named Violet,
        who works as an Auto Memory Doll, writing letters for people who cannot write themselves.
        The story follows Violet as she navigates a new life after a war, struggles to understand
        her own emotions, and seeks the meaning behind her past relationship with her commanding officer,
        Gilbert. She learns about love, grief, and other human emotions through her work and personal
        experiences, ultimately finding a sense of purpose and connection.
    </string>

    <string name="mov_yourlie_description">
        "Your Lie in April" (also known as "Shigatsu wa Kimi no Uso") is a Japanese anime and manga series that
        follows a young piano prodigy, Kousei Arima, who loses his ability to play after his mother death.
        He eventually meets an eccentric violinist, Kaori Miyazono, who helps him rediscover his passion for music,
        leading to a journey of healing and self-discovery. The series explores themes of grief, trauma, and
        the power of music in overcoming adversity.
    </string>

    <string name="mov_yourname_description">
        "Your Name" is a 2016 Japanese animated fantasy film written and directed by Makoto Shinkai,
        produced by CoMix Wave Films, and distributed by Toho. The film follows two high school students,
        Taki Tachibana and Mitsuha Miyamizu, who inexplicably begin to swap bodies.
    </string>
</resources>